<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Days Of Games</string>

    <string name="breath_of_the_wild">Legend of Zelda: Breath of the Wild</string>
    <string name="bioshock">Bioshock</string>
    <string name="crono_trigger">Chrono Trigger</string>
    <string name="super_mario_galaxy_2">Super Mario Galaxy 2</string>
    <string name="red_dead_redemption_2">Red Dead Redemption 2</string>
    <string name="super_mario_odyssey">Super Mario Odyssey</string>
    <string name="resident_evil_4">Resident Evil 4</string>
    <string name="persona_5">Persona 5: Royale</string>
    <string name="portal_2">Portal 2</string>
    <string name="ocarina_of_time">Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time</string>
    <string name="super_mario_bros_3">Super Mario Bros. 3</string>
    <string name="final_fantasy_vii">Final Fantasy VII</string>
    <string name="goldeneye">GoldenEye 007</string>
    <string name="leyend_of_zelda_the_wind_waker">Legend of Zelda: The Wind Waker</string>
    <string name="castlevania_symphony_of_the_night">Castlevania: Symphony of the Night</string>
    <string name="god_of_war">God of War</string>
    <string name="the_last_of_us">The Last of Us</string>
    <string name="elden_ring">Elden Ring</string>
    <string name="half_life_2">Half-Life 2</string>
    <string name="batman_arkham_city">Batman: Arkham City</string>
    <string name="hades">Hades</string>
    <string name="bioshock_infinite">Bioshock Infinite</string>
    <string name="grim_fandango">Grim Fandango</string>
    <string name="super_mario_world">Super Mario World</string>
    <string name="super_street_fighter_2">Super Street Fighter II X: Grand Master Challenge</string>
    <string name="tetris">Tetris</string>
    <string name="Uncharted_2">Uncharted 2: Among Thieves</string>
    <string name="metal_gear_solid">Metal Gear Solid</string>
    <string name="okami">Okami</string>
    <string name="super_smash_bros_ultimate">Super Smash Bros. Ultimate</string>"

    <string name="publishing_tlz_botw">2017</string>
    <string name="publishing_bioshock">2007</string>
    <string name="publishing_chrono_trigger">1997</string>
    <string name="publishing_smg2">2010</string>
    <string name="publishing_rdd2">2018</string>
    <string name="publishing_smo">2017</string>
    <string name="publishing_re4">2005</string>
    <string name="publishing_p5r">2019</string>
    <string name="publishing_portal_2">2011</string>
    <string name="publishing_tlz_oot">1998</string>
    <string name="publishing_smb3">1988</string>
    <string name="publishing_ffvi">1997</string>
    <string name="publishing_ge007">1997</string>
    <string name="publishing_tlz_ww">2002</string>
    <string name="publishing_cson">1997</string>
    <string name="publishing_gow">2018</string>
    <string name="publishing_lou">2013</string>
    <string name="publishing_er">2022</string>
    <string name="publishing_hf2">2004</string>
    <string name="publishing_bac">2011</string>
    <string name="publishing_hades">2018</string>
    <string name="publishing_bi">2013</string>
    <string name="publishing_gf">1998</string>
    <string name="publishing_smw">1990</string>
    <string name="publishing_sf2">1994</string>
    <string name="publishing_tetris">1984</string>
    <string name="publishing_u2">2009</string>
    <string name="publishing_mgs">1998</string>
    <string name="publishing_okami">2006</string>
    <string name="publishing_ssbu">2018</string>

    <string name="description_tlz_botw">\"Breath of the Wild\" revolutionized open-world games. Its vast, interactive Hyrule encourages free exploration and creative problem-solving. Link, with amnesia, must save Zelda and defeat Ganon, recovering memories along the way. While some criticize enemy variety, its innovative gameplay, stunning visuals, and sheer freedom make it a masterpiece.</string>
    <string name="description_bioshock">\"BioShock\" redefined narrative shooters. Its decaying Rapture immerses players in a chilling, objectivist dystopia. Jack, a plane crash survivor, must unravel the city\'s mysteries, wielding plasmids and weapons. While some find combat repetitive, its atmospheric world, thought-provoking story, and moral choices solidify its iconic status.</string>
    <string name="description_chrono_trigger">\"Chrono Trigger\" perfected time-travel RPGs. Its vibrant world spans eras, intertwining character fates. Crono and his diverse party strive to avert global destruction, battling Lavos. While its combat is classic turn based, its engaging story, memorable characters, and multiple endings cement its legendary status.</string>
    <string name="description_smg2">\"Super Mario Galaxy 2\" amplified platforming perfection. Its vibrant, gravity-defying worlds challenge Mario with inventive levels and power-ups. Mario, alongside Yoshi, pursues Bowser across the cosmos. While its story is simple, its refined gameplay, dazzling level design, and sheer joy make it a platforming masterpiece.</string>
    <string name="description_rdd2">\"Red Dead Redemption 2\" sculpted a sweeping, immersive Western masterpiece. Arthur Morgan\'s struggle for survival and loyalty amidst a dying era unfolded across a vast, breathtakingly detailed American expanse. Its deeply resonant narrative, nuanced characters, and unparalleled world construction pushed the boundaries of interactive storytelling. Though some questioned its deliberate pacing, its emotional weight and technical brilliance enshrined its legendary standing.</string>
    <string name="description_smo">\"Super Mario Odyssey\" delivered a globe-trotting platforming escapade. Mario\'s journey, powered by the transformative Cappy, spanned a diverse array of imaginative kingdoms. Its innovative capture mechanic, coupled with vibrant level design, fostered endless playful exploration. Though the plot remained simple, the sheer joy of discovery and the game\'s inventive spirit left an indelible mark on the platforming genre.</string>
    <string name="description_re4">\"Resident Evil 4\" reinvented survival horror\'s action edge. Leon Kennedy\'s rescue mission, set against a rural Spanish backdrop, unleashed a relentless wave of infected villagers. Its over-the-shoulder perspective, combined with intense, dynamic combat, forged a new standard. While its narrative leaned toward action-thriller, the game\'s gripping atmosphere and innovative gameplay left a lasting imprint on the genre.</string>
    <string name="description_p5r">\"Persona 5 Royal\" amplified the stylish, social RPG experience. Joker and the Phantom Thieves, navigating Tokyo\'s shadows and realities, challenged societal corruption. Its refined combat, expanded narrative, and deeper social links provided a richer, more immersive journey. Though its sheer length can be daunting, the game\'s captivating style and compelling themes left a profound, lasting impact.</string>
    <string name="description_portal_2">\"Portal 2\" constructed a puzzle-platforming masterpiece. Chell\'s return to Aperture Science, guided by the witty AI, GLaDOS, unveiled a deeper, more expansive narrative. Its ingenious portal mechanics, combined with clever level design and sharp humor, provided a uniquely satisfying experience. While its core gameplay remained familiar, the game\'s expanded story and collaborative co-op mode cemented its enduring imprint on puzzle games</string>
    <string name="description_tlz_oot">\"The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time\" forged a foundational 3D adventure. Link\'s journey through time, confronting Ganondorf, established a template for action-adventure games. Its innovative Z-targeting system, coupled with memorable dungeons and a sweeping narrative, revolutionized 3D gameplay. Though its graphics have aged, the game\'s enduring design and profound impact cemented its status as a landmark title.</string>
    <string name="description_smb3">\"Super Mario Bros. 3\" sculpted the very essence of expansive 2D platforming. Mario\'s adventure, unfolding across a diverse world map, pioneered a new era of side-scrolling exploration. Its arsenal of transformative power-ups, coupled with meticulously crafted kingdoms, redefined the boundaries of the genre. While its pixelated aesthetic reflects its era, the game\'s enduring design and revolutionary impact secured its legacy as a foundational masterpiece.</string>
    <string name="description_ffvi">\"Final Fantasy VI\" sculpted an emotionally rich RPG epic. A diverse ensemble of characters, each with compelling backstories, navigates a world threatened by the nihilistic Kefka. Its character-driven narrative, weaving intricate personal stories into a grand conflict, fostered a deep connection with players. The evocative world, from industrial cities to desolate landscapes, provided a compelling backdrop. Nobuo Uematsu\'s masterful score heightened emotional moments, while Kefka\'s iconic villainy left a lasting impression. This blend of narrative depth, atmospheric world-building, and unforgettable music solidified its legacy as a pinnacle of RPG design.</string>
    <string name="description_ge007">\"GoldenEye 007\" revolutionized console first-person shooters. It delivered an immersive spy thriller, with groundbreaking multiplayer and meticulously designed levels that fostered strategic gameplay. Its impact on console FPS design, and its overall quality, cemented its status as a landmark title, proving console FPS could rival their PC counterparts, and setting the stage for future console FPS experiences.</string>
    <string name="description_tlz_ww">\"The Legend of Zelda: Wind Waker\" charted a vibrant, cel-shaded course for the Zelda franchise. Link\'s seafaring adventure, set across a vast archipelago, delivered a unique exploration experience. Its distinctive art style, combined with open-world sailing and engaging dungeons, offered a fresh take on the Zelda formula. Its innovative sailing mechanics and expressive character animations, coupled with a compelling narrative, cemented its status as a beloved entry, proving the franchise\'s versatility.</string>
    <string name="description_cson">\"Castlevania: Symphony of the Night\" redefined the Metroidvania genre, crafting a gothic masterpiece of exploration and action. Alucard\'s journey through Dracula\'s castle, filled with hidden secrets and intricate level design, offered a non-linear adventure. Its RPG elements, combined with fluid combat and a haunting soundtrack, created a uniquely immersive experience. Its expansive map, diverse enemy encounters, and compelling narrative, along with its sheer replayability, cemented its status as a genre-defining classic.</string>
    <string name="description_gow">\"God of War (2018)\" reimagined the series, delivering a mature and emotionally resonant action-adventure. Kratos\'s journey with his son Atreus through Norse mythology, filled with intense combat and exploration, offered a deeply personal narrative. Its over-the-shoulder camera, combined with brutal, impactful combat and a stunningly realized world, provided a fresh perspective on the God of War formula. Its focus on character development, coupled with its seamless world design and epic boss battles, cemented its status as a landmark title, proving the franchise\'s ability to evolve.</string>
    <string name="description_lou">\"The Last of Us\" delivered a harrowing and emotionally charged post-apocalyptic journey. Joel and Ellie\'s struggle for survival across a ravaged America, filled with tense stealth and brutal combat, offered a deeply human story. Its grounded, realistic tone, combined with compelling character development and a gripping narrative, provided a uniquely immersive experience. Its focus on the relationship between Joel and Ellie, coupled with its visceral gameplay and haunting atmosphere, cemented its status as a landmark title, setting a new standard for narrative-driven action games.</string>
    <string name="description_er">\"Elden Ring\" crafted a sprawling and challenging open-world action RPG. The Tarnished\'s journey through the Lands Between, filled with formidable enemies and intricate lore, offered unparalleled freedom of exploration. Its intricate world design, combined with demanding combat and a vast array of customization options, delivered a deeply immersive experience. Its focus on player agency, coupled with its cryptic narrative and breathtaking environments, cemented its status as a landmark title, redefining the scope of open-world action RPGs.</string>
    <string name="description_hf2">\"Half-Life 2\" redefined first-person storytelling, delivering an immersive and technologically groundbreaking experience. 1  Gordon Freeman\'s return to City 17, under the oppressive Combine regime, offered a seamless blend of action and narrative. Its advanced physics engine, combined with intelligent enemy AI and a compelling world design, created a uniquely interactive environment. 2  Its focus on environmental storytelling, coupled with memorable characters and innovative gameplay mechanics, cemented its status as a landmark title, setting a new standard for first-person shooters.</string>
    <string name="description_bac">\"Batman: Arkham City\" expanded the Arkham universe, delivering a sprawling open-world experience within Gotham\'s walled-off prison. Batman\'s investigation into Hugo Strange\'s sinister plot, filled with iconic villains and intricate side quests, offered a compelling narrative. Its refined combat and gadget system, combined with a densely packed environment and engaging detective work, created a uniquely immersive superhero experience. Its focus on world-building, coupled with its memorable characters and thrilling gameplay, cemented its status as a landmark title, setting a new standard for superhero games.</string>
    <string name="description_hades">\"Hades\" masterfully blended roguelike action with compelling narrative, delivering a uniquely engaging experience. Zagreus\'s repeated attempts to escape the Underworld, aided by Olympian boons, revealed layers of intricate lore and character development. Its fluid, fast-paced combat, combined with a vibrant art style and a captivating soundtrack, created a deeply immersive atmosphere. Its focus on character relationships, coupled with its highly replayable structure and exceptional storytelling, cemented its status as a modern classic, redefining expectations for roguelike games.</string>
    <string name="description_bi">\"BioShock Infinite\" crafted a visually stunning and narratively complex experience, transporting players to the floating city of Columbia. Booker DeWitt\'s mission to rescue Elizabeth, filled with intense combat and philosophical themes, offered a thought-provoking journey. Its breathtaking environments, combined with dynamic combat and a mind-bending storyline, created a uniquely immersive atmosphere. Its focus on narrative twists, coupled with its engaging characters and exploration of complex ideas, cemented its status as a landmark title, pushing the boundaries of storytelling in video games.</string>
    <string name="description_gf">\"Grim Fandango\" delivered a unique blend of film noir and Mexican folklore, crafting a memorable adventure experience. Manny Calavera\'s journey through the Land of the Dead, filled with witty dialogue and intricate puzzles, offered a distinct narrative. Its distinctive art style, combined with a jazzy soundtrack and memorable characters, created a deeply atmospheric experience. Its clever writing, coupled with its engaging story and unique setting, cemented its status as a cult classic, proving the power of imaginative storytelling in adventure games.</string>
    <string name="description_smw">\"Super Mario World\" expanded the 2D platforming genre, delivering a vibrant and expansive adventure on Dinosaur Land. Mario\'s quest to rescue Princess Peach from Bowser, filled with hidden secrets and diverse environments, offered a rich gameplay experience. Its introduction of Yoshi, combined with cleverly designed levels and a seamless world map, created a uniquely engaging experience. Its focus on exploration, coupled with its polished gameplay and charming aesthetic, cemented its status as a platforming masterpiece, setting a new standard for 16-bit platformers.</string>
    <string name="description_sf2">\"Super Street Fighter II X: Grand Master Challenge\" refined the competitive fighting game genre, delivering the definitive iteration of the Street Fighter II series. This title perfected the formula with enhanced gameplay mechanics, including Super Combos and increased speed, fostering intense and strategic matches. Its introduction of the secret character Akuma, combined with finely tuned character balance and a polished presentation, created a highly competitive experience. Its focus on precise controls and deep gameplay, coupled with its enduring popularity in arcades and tournaments, cemented its status as a fighting game classic, setting a high standard for competitive play.</string>
    <string name="description_tetris">\"Tetris\" crafted a timeless puzzle experience, delivering a deceptively simple yet endlessly engaging game. The falling tetrominoes, requiring strategic placement to clear lines, offered a pure and addictive challenge. Its minimalist design, combined with its intuitive gameplay and universal appeal, created a uniquely accessible experience. Its focus on spatial reasoning, coupled with its enduring popularity across generations, cemented its status as a puzzle game icon, defining the genre\'s enduring appeal.</string>
    <string name="description_u2">\"Uncharted 2: Among Thieves\" elevated cinematic action-adventure games, delivering a thrilling and visually spectacular experience. Nathan Drake\'s pursuit of Marco Polo\'s lost fleet, filled with breathtaking set pieces and engaging characters, offered a captivating narrative. Its refined gameplay, combined with stunning environments and a robust multiplayer mode, created a uniquely immersive experience. Its focus on dynamic action sequences, coupled with its compelling story and polished presentation, cemented its status as a landmark title, setting a new benchmark for action-adventure games.</string>
    <string name="description_mgs">\"Metal Gear Solid\" revolutionized stealth-action gaming, delivering a cinematic and immersive experience. Solid Snake\'s infiltration of Shadow Moses, filled with complex characters and a gripping narrative, offered a new standard for storytelling. Its innovative stealth mechanics, combined with groundbreaking 3D graphics and a memorable soundtrack, created a uniquely engaging atmosphere. Its focus on mature themes, coupled with its intricate plot and memorable boss battles, cemented its status as a landmark title, setting a new benchmark for stealth games and cinematic presentation.</string>
    <string name="description_okami">\"Okami\" crafted a visually stunning and culturally rich adventure, delivering a unique experience inspired by Japanese mythology. Amaterasu\'s journey to restore life to Nippon, utilizing the Celestial Brush techniques, offered a captivating narrative. Its distinctive sumi-e art style, combined with a beautiful soundtrack and engaging gameplay, created a deeply immersive atmosphere. Its focus on exploration and puzzle-solving, coupled with its charming characters and vibrant world, cemented its status as a cult classic, proving the power of artistic vision in video games.</string>
    <string name="description_ssbu">\"Super Smash Bros. Ultimate\" delivered the definitive crossover fighting experience, uniting a vast roster of iconic video game characters. This title perfected the series\' formula with refined gameplay mechanics, an expansive "World of Light" adventure mode, and a staggering amount of content. Its unprecedented character selection, combined with a wealth of stages and musical tracks, created a celebration of gaming history. Its focus on accessibility and depth, coupled with its robust multiplayer options and constant stream of updates, cemented its status as a genre-defining masterpiece, solidifying its place as a cornerstone of modern fighting games.</string>

    <string name="author_tlz_botw">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="author_bioshock">2K Games</string>
    <string name="author_chrono_trigger">Square Enix</string>
    <string name="author_smg2">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="author_rdd2">Rockstar Games</string>
    <string name="author_smo">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="author_re4">Capcom</string>
    <string name="author_p5r">Atlus</string>
    <string name="author_portal_2">Valve</string>
    <string name="author_tlz_oot">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="author_smb3">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="author_ffvi">Square Enix</string>
    <string name="author_ge007">Rare</string>
    <string name="author_tlz_ww">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="author_cson">Konami</string>
    <string name="author_gow">Santa Monica Studio</string>
    <string name="author_lou">Naughty Dog</string>
    <string name="author_er">FromSoftware</string>
    <string name="author_hf2">Valve</string>
    <string name="author_bac">Rocksteady Studios</string>
    <string name="author_hades">Supergiant Games</string>
    <string name="author_bi">2K Games</string>
    <string name="author_gf">LucasArts</string>
    <string name="author_smw">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="author_sf2">Capcom</string>
    <string name="author_tetris">Various (originally Alexey Pajitnov)</string>
    <string name="author_u2">Naughty Dog</string>
    <string name="author_mgs">Konami</string>
    <string name="author_okami">Clover Studio</string>
    <string name="author_ssbu">Nintendo</string>
    <string name="expand_button">See more or less information.</string>

</resources>